<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Submission1</string>
    <string name="nama_movie">nama movie</string>
    <string name="deskrpisi">Deskripsi</string>

    <string-array name="data_movies_name">
        <item>Aquaman</item>
        <item>Avengers</item>
        <item>Bumblebee</item>
        <item>Deadpool</item>
        <item>How to Train Your Dragon</item>
        <item>Dragon Ball Super</item>
        <item>Preman Pensiun</item>
        <item>Hunter Killer</item>
        <item>Spider Man</item>
        <item>Venom</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_movies_description">
        <item>Arthur Curry learns that he is the heir to the underwater kingdom of Atlantis, and must step forward to lead his people and to be a hero to the world.</item>
        <item>"Avengers: Infinity War is a 2018 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team the Avengers, produced by Marvel Studios and distributed by Walt Disney Studios Motion Pictures. It is the sequel to 2012's The Avengers and 2015's Avengers: Age of Ultron, and the nineteenth film in the Marvel Cinematic Universe (MCU)."</item>
        <item>On the run in the year 1987, Bumblebee finds refuge in a junkyard in a small Californian beach town. Charlie, on the cusp of turning 18 and trying to find her place in the world, discovers Bumblebee, battle-scarred and broken. When Charlie revives him, she quickly learns this is no ordinary yellow VW bug.</item>
        <item>"A kidnapped Fred Savage is forced to endure Deadpool's PG-13 rendition of Deadpool 2 as a Princess Bride-esque story that's full of magic, wonder and zero F's."</item>
        <item>As Hiccup fulfills his dream of creating a peaceful dragon utopia, Toothless discovery of an untamed, elusive mate draws the Night Fury away. When danger mounts at home and Hiccup’s reign as village chief is tested, both dragon and rider must make impossible decisions to save their kind.</item>
        <item>The theme for this remarkable new film will be Saiyan, the strongest race in the universe. Since Battle of Gods, Goku has undergone new forms from Super Saiyan God to Super Saiyan Blue to other evolved forms that have gone up against many invincible warriors from multiple universes. This new story will focus on the origin of the Saiyans strength and what it means to be Saiyan.</item>
        <item>After three years, the business of Muslihat, who has retired as a thug, has a problem. Sales decline. Muslihat also faces new problems when Safira, her only daughter, grows up in adolescence and begins to be visited by boys. A bigger problem: frictions between his former subordinates.</item>
        <item>An untested American submarine captain teams with U.S. Navy Seals to rescue the Russian president, who has been kidnapped by a rogue general.</item>
        <item>A big-screen animated take on Spider-Man featuring Miles Morales, an Afro-Latino New York teen who is endowed with amazing powers similar to those of Peter Parker after a bite from a genetically engineered spider.</item>
        <item>Investigative journalist Eddie Brock attempts a comeback following a scandal, but accidentally becomes the host of Venom, a violent, super powerful alien symbiote. Soon, he must rely on his newfound powers to protect the world from a shadowy organization looking for a symbiote of their own.</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="data_movie_photo">
        <item>@drawable/poster_aquaman </item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_avengerinfinity</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bumblebee</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_deadpool</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragon</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragonball</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_preman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_hunterkiller</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_spiderman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_venom</item>
    </array>


    <string-array name="data_movie_genre">
    <item>Action, Adventure, Fantasy</item>
    <item>Action, Adventure, Sci-Fi</item>
    <item>Action, Adventure, Sci-Fi</item>
    <item>Comedy, Action</item>
    <item>Animation, Action, Adventure</item>
    <item>Animation, Action, Adventure, Comedy</item>
    <item>Comedy, Drama</item>
    <item>Action, Thriller</item>
    <item>Animation, Action, Adventure</item><item>Action, Sci-Fi, Thriller</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="data_movie_production">
    <item>Dc Comics, Dc Entertainment, Warner Bros</item>
    <item>Marvel Studios</item>
    <item>Hasbro, Paramount, Allspark Pictures</item>
    <item>Marvel Entertainment, 20th Century Fox</item>
    <item>Dreamworks Animation, Universal Pictures</item>
    <item>Toei Animation, Fox International Productions, Shueisha</item>
    <item>Mnc Pictures</item>
    <item>Original Film, G-base, Millennium Films</item>
    <item>Columbia Pictures, Sony Pictures, Sony Pictures Animation</item>
    <item>Avi Arad Productions, Matt Tolmach Productions, Pascal Pictures</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_movie_duration">
    <item>143 Minutes</item>
    <item>149 Minutes</item>
    <item>113 Minutes</item>
    <item>118 Minutes</item>
    <item>104 Minutes</item>
    <item>100 Minutes</item>
    <item>95 Minutes</item>
    <item>121 Minutes</item>
    <item>116 Minutes</item>
    <item>112 Minutes</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_movie_relaese">
    <item>21 December 2018</item>
    <item>25 April 2018</item>
    <item>21 December 2018</item>
    <item>18 December 2018</item>
    <item>22 February 2019</item>
    <item>14 December 2018</item>
    <item>17 January 2019</item>
    <item>26 October 2018</item>
    <item>14 December 2018</item>
    <item>05 October 2018</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
